[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":92391,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":115757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":2337,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":118095,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":15679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":133775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1070,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":134846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3636,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":138483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":608,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":139092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0","6","0"],"rt":5101,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":144194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":848,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":145043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":147364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":731,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":148096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1287,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":149384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 + <sub>6</ sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":587,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":149972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":1822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":151795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":500,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":152297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":1573,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":153871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":592,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":154464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your r esult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2074,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":156539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":486,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":157026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1722,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":158749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":496,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":159246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":1675,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":160921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":559,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":161480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":5771,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":167254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inver se under  +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":26944,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":194200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4330,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":198532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":199493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><b r /> (Re member, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1580,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":201074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":725,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":201800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":203164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":424,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":203589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":1509,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":205099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<su b>6</sub >.","rt":415,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":205514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":207649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":552,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":208202,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be pe rformed  starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":17193,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":225395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, bu t there  is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":10607,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":236003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":9638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":245643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":8388,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":254031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remem ber, a g enerator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2124,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":256155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":893,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":257049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remembe r, a gen erator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":1641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":258691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":746,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":259438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2084,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":261523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1038,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":262562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure y ou under stand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":9895,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":272458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":275040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":720,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":275761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":1939,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":277702,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":283977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":286804,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":289513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3854,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":293368,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":6406,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":299774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</ sub> 1?  Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4+1 = 5 < 9, so there is nothing else to be done.","explanation_history":["4+1 = 5 < 9, so there is nothing else to be done."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":20359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":320134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4 = 12 > 9 so 12-9=3.","explanation_history":["8+4 = 12 >9 ","8+4 = 12 >9","8+4 = 12 > 9 do","8+4 = 12 > 9 d","8+4 = 12 > 9 so 12-9=3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":13955,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":334090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</ sub>? Pl ease explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Not sure","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solution 0-8 and see which one gives all numbers. That would take a while.","explanation_history":["I don't exactly remember what identiy was (","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number ","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If t","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If thats","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solu","I don't exactly remember what iden tity was  (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible sol","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible so","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible s","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solutions ","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solutions","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solution 0=","I don't exactly remember what  identit y was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solution 0-9","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solution 0-9","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solution 0-8 and see which one gives all numbers. That woud","I don't exactly remember what identity was (was it the number that results in every other number?). If that's what it is then I would just try every possible solution 0-8 and see which one gives all numbers. That would take a while."],"response_history":["Not sure"],"rt":90422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":424513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":7298,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":431812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":3870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":435683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Nothing","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Nothing"],"rt":8999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":444683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12 -0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 which is equal to 9, so 9-9 = 0. The inverse is the number added to it that results in 0.","explanation_history":["9","-","9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 =","9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 which is equal to 9, so 0=","9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 which is equal to 9, so 0","9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 which is equal to 9, so 9-9 =0.","9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 which is equal to 9, so 9-9 =0","9-3=6, so 3+6 = 9 which is equal to 9, so 9-9 = 0. The inverse is the number added to it that results in 0."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":35688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":480372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Y es","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6 8\n2+7 0\n2+8 1\n\nAll numbers are accounted for","explanation_history":["2=","2+0\n2+1\n2+2\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7+","2+0\n2+1\n2+2\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 \n2+1\n2+2\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1\n2+2\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 \n2+2\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 \n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4\n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 \n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 \n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 \n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6\n2+7\n2+8","2+0  2\n2+1 3 \n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6 \n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6 8\n2+7\n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6 8\n2+7 \n2+8","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6 8\n2+7 0\n2+8 1\n\nAll numbers are accountd","2+0 2\n2+1 3\n2+2 4 \n2+3 5\n2+4 6\n2+5 7\n2+6 8\n2+7 0\n2+8 1\n\nAll numbers are accounted for"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":68109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":548482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 1\n3+8 2\n\nAll numbers accounted for again","explanation_history":["3 0","3 ","3+0\n3+1+","3+0\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4+","3+0\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n35","3+0\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3 +8\n3+9","3+0\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n3+","3+0\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n3","3+0\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 \n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 \n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 \n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 \n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 \n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 \n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 \n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 \n3+8\n"," 3+0 3\n3 +1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 1\n3+8\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 1\n3+8 \n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 1\n3+8 1\n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 1\n3+8 \n","3+0 3\n3+1 4\n3+2 5\n3+3 6\n3+4 7\n3+5 8\n3+6 0\n3+7 1\n3+8 2\n\nAll numbers accounted for again"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":57032,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":605515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers accounted for\n","explanation_history":["50\n51\n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n59","50\n51\n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n5","50\n51\n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 \n51\n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51\n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 \n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 \n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53\n 54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 \n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 \n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 \n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 \n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 \n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 \n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\n\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\na\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nal\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall \n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall n\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall nu\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall num\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbe\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall number\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers \n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers a\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers ac\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers acco\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers accou\n","50 5\n51 6\n5 2 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers account\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers accounte\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers accounted \n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers accounted fo\n","50 5\n51 6\n52 7\n53 8\n54 0\n55 1\n56 2\n57 3\n58 4\n\nall numbers accounted for\n"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":49168,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":654684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am I doing this right?)\n","explanation_history":["60\n61\n62\n63\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 \n61\n62\n63\n64\n65\n66\n6 7\n68\n","60 6\n61\n62\n63\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 \n62\n63\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62\n63\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 \n63\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 \n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 \n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 \n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 \n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 2\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 \n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 \n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\n\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67  4\n68 5\n\nal\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall n\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall nu\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall num\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbe\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall number\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers ac\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers acco\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accou\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounte\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2 \n66 3\n 67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted f\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i d\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i do\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doin\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2 \n66 3\n 67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing t\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing th\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this \n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this r\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this ri\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this righ\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this right\n","60 6\n 61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am i doing this right?\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am  doing this right?\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am I doing this right?\n","60 6\n61 7\n62 8\n63 0\n64 1\n65 2\n66 3\n67 4\n68 5\n\nall numbers accounted for (am I doing this right?)\n"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":45505,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":700190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":20928,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":721119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n - 1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n - 1"],"rt":11971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":733091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n - x = y","explain":true,"explanation":"The inverse is whatever is added to x to result in x +n y = 0","explanation_history":["The inverse is whatever is addd ","The inverse is whatever is addd","The inverse is whatever is added to x to result in x +n y = o","The inverse is whatever is added to x to result in x +n y =  0"],"response_history":["n - ","n - x ","n - x = y"],"rt":33693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":766785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm not sure."],"rt":11918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":778704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":8508,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":787213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":3911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":791125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":6872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":797999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14 -0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm not sure how to start to solve this.","explanation_history":["I'm not sure how to start to solove thi","I'm not sure how to start to solove th","I'm not sure how to start to solove t","I'm not sure how to start to solove ","I'm not sure how to start to solove","I'm not sure how to start to solov","I'm not sure how to start to solo","I'm not sure how to start to solve this."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":814438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"mul ti","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":73496,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":887935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlier and wish I could see it again.","explanation_history":["i'd li","I'd like to take this box to adm it that  the generator","I'd like to take this box to admit that the generato","I'd like to take this box to admit that the gen","I'd like to take this box to admit that the ge","I'd like to take this box to admit that the g","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept on","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I t","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlir ad ","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlir ad","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it  until I  started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlir a","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlir ","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlir","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlierand","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlieran","I'd like to take this box to admi t that t he concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earliera","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlier and wis ","I'd like to take this box to admit that the concept of generators is confusing to me. I thought I understood it until I started doing it and explaining it earlier. I guess I didn't understand what I read earlier and wish I could see it again."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":78596,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":966533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":4277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":970810,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1343,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":972154,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"22","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["22"],"rt":1826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":973981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high  school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree","Associates Degree","Some college, no degree"],"rt":4902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":978884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calc 3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Calc 3"],"rt":7767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":986653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar ar e you wi th the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"5 - used it, remember and understand it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5 - used it, remember and understand it","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"rt":5946,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":992599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remem ber and  understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":2666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":995266,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":997745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":1600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":999346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1000750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1002942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/a re your  native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Emg;osj","English"],"rt":5116,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1008059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2604,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1010664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4226,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1014891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]